<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>LGT news</title>
    <link>https://www.lgt.com/en/lgtnews.xml</link>
    <description>Thank you, you have subscribed to a  RSS feed  containing LGT Company News and Research News.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <dc:language>en</dc:language>
    <item>
      <title>Empire State Index falls to six-year low</title>
      <link>https://www.lgt.com/en/news/Empire-State-Index-falls-to-six-year-low/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bad news from the U.S., where the Federal Reserve Bank of New York&amp;#8217;s Empire State manufacturing index slumped to a six-year low as a stronger US dollar is hurting exports. The plunged to minus 14.9 in August, the lowest level since April 2009, from 3.9 the prior month.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2015 07:16:36 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.lgt.com/en/news/Empire-State-Index-falls-to-six-year-low/</guid>
      <dc:date>2015-08-18T07:16:36Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japan contracts on weaker consumption</title>
      <link>https://www.lgt.com/en/news/Japan-contracts-on-weaker-consumption/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Japan&amp;#8217;s economy contracted in Q2 as consumers and businesses cut spending and exports tumbled. Gross domestic product fell at an annualized rate of -1.6%, comparted to a +4.5% growth rate in Q1.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2015 06:40:44 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.lgt.com/en/news/Japan-contracts-on-weaker-consumption/</guid>
      <dc:date>2015-08-17T06:40:44Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>US retail sales point to solid consumer spending</title>
      <link>https://www.lgt.com/en/news/US-retail-sales-point-to-solid-consumer-spending/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Following the global slump in equity markets after China&amp;#8217;s currency devaluation in the first half of this week, stocks have stabilized somewhat. A positive signal came from US retail sales, which rose +0.6% in July compared to the previous month. July&amp;#8217;s gain was broad-based with 11 of 13 major categories advancing, pointing to solid consumer spending in the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2015 06:43:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.lgt.com/en/news/US-retail-sales-point-to-solid-consumer-spending/</guid>
      <dc:date>2015-08-14T06:43:59Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LGT Beacon: Japan`s corporate earnings surge continues</title>
      <link>https://www.lgt.com/en/news/LGT-Beacon-Japans-corporate-earnings-surge-continues-00001/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We have been overweighting Japan&amp;#8217;s equity market since early 2013, believing that Tokyo&amp;#8217;s decision to finally pursue uninhibited monetary policy easing and market-friendly reforms would trigger a strong and sustained corporate earnings rebound.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2015 06:58:08 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.lgt.com/en/news/LGT-Beacon-Japans-corporate-earnings-surge-continues-00001/</guid>
      <dc:date>2015-08-12T06:58:08Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LGT Beacon: Stock market earthquake in China</title>
      <link>https://www.lgt.com/en/news/LGT-Beacon-Stock-market-earthquake-in-China-00001/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In recent weeks, China has experienced a stock market earthquake. While the domestic A-share market was suffering the most, the H-share market in Hong Kong which is freely accessible for international investors has also reported ample losses. However, other emerging markets let alone the global bull market have been only marginally shaken by the Chinese earthquake.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 07:07:09 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.lgt.com/en/news/LGT-Beacon-Stock-market-earthquake-in-China-00001/</guid>
      <dc:date>2015-08-05T07:07:09Z</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LGT Beacon: Malaysia shaken by political turbulences</title>
      <link>https://www.lgt.com/en/news/LGT-Beacon-Malaysia-shaken-by-political-turbulences-00001/</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Malaysia has lately caused negative headlines worldwide because of unprofitable and opaque investment practices of its state investment vehicle 1Malaysia Development Berhad (1MDB). Allegations range from misallocations to wastage and enrichment. While not only political, but also cyclical headwinds are cause for concern, solid fundamentals allow for a positive long-term outlook.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2015 06:44:02 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.lgt.com/en/news/LGT-Beacon-Malaysia-shaken-by-political-turbulences-00001/</guid>
      <dc:date>2015-07-29T06:44:02Z</dc:date>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>

